<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Y5C4L3</title>
    <link>https://y5c4l3.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Y5C4L3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 y5c4l3</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 23:27:07 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://y5c4l3.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding DTE &amp; DCE: SystemVerilog&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>https://y5c4l3.net/2024/06/10/understanding-dte-dce-systemverilog-s-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 23:27:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://y5c4l3.net/2024/06/10/understanding-dte-dce-systemverilog-s-perspective/</guid>
      <description>Intro RS-232 is a common electrical interface standard for communications, often physically presented as a DE-9 connector, and people today consistently run UART over it. But with a closer look at the standard TIA/EIA-232-F, readers will find some weird concepts like DTE and DCE. They often appear in many specifications published by TIA.
Searching DTE &amp;amp; DCE on the internet, people tend to present PCs and MODEMs connected to PSTN and assert that</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recovering RSA-512 Key Pair with Distributed CADO-NFS</title>
      <link>https://y5c4l3.net/2023/08/19/recovering-rsa-key-pair-with-cado-nfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://y5c4l3.net/2023/08/19/recovering-rsa-key-pair-with-cado-nfs/</guid>
      <description>Intro RSA is currently the most widely used public-key cryptosystem in the world. In public-key cryptography, there are two kinds of keys: private keys and public keys. Private keys are generated by some algorithm and need to be kept secret by the operator. Public keys are directly derived from private keys and can be published publicly anywhere. A public key together with the private key which it&amp;rsquo;s derived from is called a key pair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://y5c4l3.net/writing-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://y5c4l3.net/writing-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Guidelines here spread consistency to the articles in form. More importantly they may help the readers to understand the contents better.
Formats Paragraphs Block(-like) Semantics Require Additional Newline For block semantic elements, it must be followed by an additional newline, so that goldmark will generate the paragraph p, otherwise some visual styles may not be correctly applied.
Characters Punctuation Simple Marks The difference between CJK and Western punctuation is still relatively large, so the punctuation set of the article should be related to the main language of the article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring NPTv6 and More on H3C Routers</title>
      <link>https://y5c4l3.net/2023/08/15/configuring-nptv6-on-h3c-routers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://y5c4l3.net/2023/08/15/configuring-nptv6-on-h3c-routers/</guid>
      <description>Intro IPv6 is the successor to IPv4, but many necessities of IPv6 are still in development, which include a wide range of infrastructures (hardware / software), specifications (IETF RFCs), good practices followed by ISPs, and awareness of developers.
In home scenarios, many ISPs do allocate IPv6 prefixes for end-users via DHCPv6 PD (probably over PPPoE).
Even if the prefix is dynamic (changing on each dial or a daily basis), this is still quite good for most home users as long as they are using EXACTLY one router with decent support for dual-stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://y5c4l3.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://y5c4l3.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Y5C4L3 Y5C4L3 is a tech worker / enthusiast from China 🇨🇳. He has completed his Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in computer science, and is now focusing on programming language theories, computer graphics and software security.
👨‍💻 Computing 🖥️ PC 💻 Laptop Hei[1]: ThinkPad P15v Gen 3 Aug 2022 &amp;ndash; now
OS: Arch Linux 🖥️ Desktop Daleth Jun 2020 &amp;ndash; now
Motherboard: MSI MPG Z490 GAMING PLUS (MS-7C75)
CPU: Intel Core i7-10700K (Comet Lake)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, world!</title>
      <link>https://y5c4l3.net/2023/01/31/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 15:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://y5c4l3.net/2023/01/31/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello, world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>https://y5c4l3.net/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 11:24:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://y5c4l3.net/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>